# Sihaya Harris

UX // Product Designer

sihayaharris@gmail.com (618) 623-9302 Brooklyn, NY

Portfolio: <a href="https://sihayaharris.netlify.app">https://sihayaharris.netlify.app</a> LinkedIn: <a href="https://sihayaharris/netlify.app">www.linkedin.com/in/sihaya-harris/netlify.app</a> LinkedIn:

#### **SKILLS**

**Design tools:** 

Figma Adobe XD Illustrator Photoshop InDesign

UX/UI:

design systems
design thinking
wireframing
mockups
prototyping
storyboarding
affinity diagrams
brainstorming
information architecture
usability testing

Web development:

HTML CSS

**JavaScript** 

React

SQL

MongoDB

responsive web design

### **AWARDS**

Bombay Sapphire/ Canvas Project/ featured finalist/ August 2021 Prospective UX Design Intern, Highly motivated User Experience, Interaction design, and product design generalist distinguished by a penchant for innovative and analytical thinking, verbal communication, and multimedia collaboration. Background includes customer service, art and design.

### **PROJECTS**

MessageGhost | **UX Researcher**, **UX & UI designer** | August 2023 Prototype: <a href="https://adobe.ly/3Pn2PeF">https://adobe.ly/3Pn2PeF</a>

- Message/writing composition app incorporating AI
- Responsive design, built for desktop, tablet, and mobile

Planting | UX Researcher, UX & UI designer | June 2023

Prototype: https://bit.ly/3nsAVCd

Figma, Gardening app that works like a living farmer's almanac

QRad | Originator and Lead Developer | March 2022

Repo: https://bit.ly/3MGGuo5 Live: https://bit.ly/3MU3OyT

- Digital business card with QR codes that allows users to make networking exchanges
- React, MongoDB, GraphQL, Node.js, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Freelance Web Designer**

January 2022 - present | Brooklyn, NY

- Designed applications through research, wireframing, prototyping, usability testing, and iteration
- Developed designs into full-stack applications

### Bartender, Littlefield

Feb 2023 - present | Brooklyn, NY

 Optimized system for service saving time by up to 20% and increasing sales potential

## **Bartender, Coney Island Brewery**

April 2023 - present | Brooklyn, NY

 Collaborated in the brewery's highest-grossing events, including Mermaid Parade when we served more than 1,000 guests, and Fourth of July which grossed over 30K

### Bartender, Canary Club

May 2022 - April 2023 | New York, NY

- Maintained a high standard of service and technical knowledge, increasing yearly profit by 30%
- Collaborated in highest grossing service of company's history pulling in over 50K in just one night

### **EDUCATION**

Google UX Certificate | January 2022 - August 2023 | online Certificate in Full Stack Development | September 2021 - March 2022 Columbia School of Engineering, NY, NY

**Bachelors in Painting,** Summa cum laude | August/2008 - May/2012 Savannah College of Art & Design, Savannah, Ga